Contato

Rua Manuel Martins da Hora, 12 3D. Mobile: +351 918.052.210
Residence: +351 912.499.019
E-mail address - valdimirmartins@uol.com.br +351 918.052.210 (Home) valdimirmartins@uol.com.br

www.linkedin.com/in/valdimirmartins-santos-15874632 (LinkedIn)

Principais competências

Accounting
Internal Controls
ERP

Languages

Ingles e Espanhol

Certifications

Negociação Estratégica

Fundamentos de Gestão de Projetos: Comunicação

Fundamentos do Planejamento Estratégico

Lottatogioo

MBA FINANCAS

O Poder do Coaching no Desenvolvimento dos Colaboradores

Valdimir Martins Santos

Corporate Financial Controller | in Transition.

Lisboa, Lisboa, Portugal

Resumo

 Goal-oriented Financial Controller offering 15 years' experience within non-profit and for-profit organizations. Expert in advising business executives to achieve financial goals and growth targets.
 Accomplished in improving financial operations by introducing robust internal controls, processes and standards.

Experiência

Autônomo

Corporate Financial Controller fevereiro de 2018 - Present (2 anos 2 meses)

Lisboa e Região, Portugal

Autonomo

Empreeendedor

maio de 2018 - Present (1 ano 11 meses)

Sao Paulo

Empreendedor

Consultor - CFO.

maio de 2018 - Present (1 ano 11 meses)

São Paulo

FDAG Art Galery Chief Financial Officer abril de 2017 - abril de 2018 (1 ano 1 mês)

São Paulo e Região, Brasil

JVC KENWOOD Holdings Inc,

Finance Controller

janeiro de 2013 - fevereiro de 2018 (5 anos 2 meses)

- •Management of all financial, human resources and information-technology activities in Brazil, including cash flow, treasury, tax and budget planning.
- •Responsible for ensuring veracity and transparency of financial information and reports submitted to the several managerial levels at JVC Kenwood Japan.
- And all similar tax issues

JVCKENWOOD BRAZIL FINANCE CONTROLLER janeiro de 2013 - março de 2017 (4 anos 3 meses)

Jafra Cosmetics

Finance Controller

fevereiro de 2010 - outubro de 2012 (2 anos 9 meses)

responsible for all financial transactions in Brazil, regarding strategic and managerial levels, in order to assure the opportunity and veracity of the finance information prepared, and submitted to the different managements, local, Jafra México, Worldwide and Vorwerk arising from the finance operations. Also assure the compliance and reinforcing the internal control that allows the correct maintenance of the assets and the strict compliance and adhesion to the prescribed administrative policies as well as the compliance with the legal, fiscal, labor, local, federal and governmental statutes.

Outstanding achievements: Implementation of tax planning covering the amt of BRL 15.000K.

Key manager in order to figure out to the Board the directions of the business providing the clearest explanations about Brazilian it's taxes issues going to Implementing new business in Brazil.

PwC

Outsourcing Project Manager fevereiro de 2009 - janeiro de 2010 (1 ano)

Responsible for managing several Outsourcing's Services projects to nationals and Multinational companies as Mc Donalds, C. A Computer Associates, Procter and Gamble, Google.

Going to provide solutions to departments as Financial, Logistics, Accounting, and Controlling Costs International, foreign exchange, import and export, design and supervision of final trial balance and balance sheet, budgeting, including monitoring and comparison with reality, control of cash flow, negotiating with banks. Internationally I am responsible for the information

presented in monthly reports as UK GAAP (Monthly Balance Sheet properly translated to the criteria of U.S. GAAP) providing the necessary clarifications to the Internal Audit International (USA) as regards the analysis of the Operation Performance in Brazil.

BD0 - Trevisan Independent Auditors and Audit Outsourcing S / C Lt. Outsourcing Project Manager - Finance, Accounting, Tax, HR, International Reports

março de 2009 - dezembro de 2009 (10 meses)

Position - Outsourcing Project Manager - Finance, Accounting, Tax, HR, International Reports.

Report: Brazil Regional CEO, European Finance Director

Subordinates: 19 direct

Formação acadêmica

ISEG - Lisbon School of Economics & Management Pos Graducao, Tecnologia da Informação · (2018 - 2019)

Centro Universitário Nove de Julho
MBA - FINANCAS CORPORATIVAS, FINANCES · (2004 - 2005)

Centro Universitario Ibero Americana
Bachelor of Business Administration (B.B.A.), Accounting and
Finance · (1990 - 1995)